Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Tim
Dylan Show. How are you? I have a
Netflix special coming out on Tuesday,
April 15th. What I'd like you to do
right now, my little demon hose, is go
on to Netflix and hit the reminder to be
reminded that this special comes. I
don't care if your child is in
anaphylactic shock. Hit it with the EPI.
put the reminder on Netflix to be
reminded to watch when the special goes
live. It is Tuesday the 15th, right?
Yeah. Tuesday, April 15th. I'm in the
midst of a press tour. Is it Megan
Kelly's home today? Lovely, lovely
property. And um I'm all over the place
going down to see Joe Rogan in Austin
and Tom Christina and
others. So, that would help out a lot if
you put uh the
reminder on Netflix. What does it look?
Can you go to Netflix and show them how
to do it? Maybe people are
confused. You're going to love
it. It's very fun. We have a fun promo
that's coming out that no one will be
angry at at all.
I'll just say that this helicopter crash
in the Hudson's driving me
nuts because number one, I'm not a
devote of the
helicopter. But I'll tell you this, it
is convenient as
hell every now and then to hop in a
helicopter from Manhattan and go to the
Hamptons, but you don't want to end up
dead.
So, it's becoming a
problem. I'm just saying it's
flight can't be for all people
anymore. Everyone can't be in the air.
People that are in the air need it's got
to be people that have deser that
deserve to be in the air.
Not all not everyone is not gonna it's
not for everyone. Helicopter tours need
to go away. What do you need to
see? New York is the most famous
man-made vista in the world. It is the
most famous skyline on
Earth. What do you you get? Get go to a
a rooftop bar and get a view. Go to an
observation deck.
Don't get in a helicopter with your
family. You're taking a
chance. Especially the [__]
helicopter
tours. You don't know who the [__] is in
there or what they're doing. I'm telling
you enough with these summer vacations.
I'm predicting this summer because of
the market
instability that people are going to
actually find ways to have vacations at
their house. It's called a station where
you don't leave your home. And your kids
go, "Are we going anywhere?" And you go,
"Shut
up." And they go, "Well, actually, John
and his family are going somewhere." Go,
"Yeah, yeah, we we got cleaned out.
We're
[__] John's family owns property.
We're [__] here. We got
nothing. Oh, they're going to the lake.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Good. Good. I hope he
drowns. I hope John drowns in the lake
with his family. His father's a
drunk. He's always nice to me. Shut up.
I have nothing. This family has nothing.
That's the
conversations that will be happening
this summer. When the kids go, "Are we
going anywhere?" The answer is no. We're
not. We're not going anywhere. Kids are
spoiled pieces of [__] They're making
you feel bad about the economy. They're
the problem. Oh, consumer confidence is
plunging because kids want more [__]
than they [__] need. By the way, oh,
there's going to be less Christmas pre
Good. Good. There should be none. You
should get one [__]
present. This abundance that everybody
talks about is every Nobody's happy, by
the way. So, enough with this crap.
Nova, get get off. Get out of the
helicopter. It is a convenient way for
me to
go and and we fly mostly when the water
is warm. That doesn't mean much if it
goes down, you know, and it kind of
spirals. I don't even want to show this
video. This is terrible. This is a a
family uh that crashed and and just show
it just to scare people because I think
people got to stay out of these things.
Show it. In a matter of seconds, a
helicopter fell from the sky. God, the
news people don't help, do they? In a
matter of
seconds, what started out as a family
trip quickly ended in a watery
grave. In a matter of seconds, a once
smiling family plunged to their death in
lower Manhattan. The cold waters of the
early spring Hudson were the last thing
that family felt. It's like, do we need
that? What is this guy? Is this guy's
reaction now?
Like it sounded like like a engine just
died and I just it was like do and I
just turned I looked and I saw the
helicopter um crash and splash into the
water. Yo, good, good, good. Well, I'm
glad we got his tank. This guy, I saw it
crash and smash into the water. I heard
the helicopter went down into the
water. Oh,
good. Well, I'm happy. I'm happy that
we've cleared that up. We were all
confused. What really happened? What
exactly
happened? Everyone's So, it's like
everybody's like, "What exactly
happened? I saw this helicopter and then
it fell out of the sky and into the
water."
What was the first woman? Did the first
woman I just want one of them to go like
I don't know if it was even in the air.
I can't believe anything anymore.
Was like screaming. We were crying.
Claiming S River. Everybody was like
screaming. We were crying. Claiming six
lives including a family on a
sightseeing trip.
You got to stay out of the helicop. You
got to stay out. You got to You got to
stay
out for the sake of your family. You got
to You got to prepare your children now
for actually it's lean lean times. Lean
times. Market's up, the market's down.
There's a lot of volatility. Larry
thinks go, we're going to have a
recession. Jamie Diamond, all these
guys, the the real demons are out here
talking about the recession. CEOs of all
these big banks of private equity
companies are going, "We're going to
we're going to have a recession." And
you know, you're gonna have to tell your
children and prepare them for a This is
not going to be the epic summer. It's
not going to be epic. Too many people
expect everything to all these kids
going to
Coachella. It's epic. It's going to be
what? It's the times of our lives, you
know. Well, we're going to have to we're
going to have to calm that down. We're
not going to have the times of our lives
this summer. It's going to be uh try not
to die. That's what you tell your
children. try not to die this summer
because hopefully next summer or the
summer after we can go back to doing
something. But we're gonna have a little
It's a rough
patch here. It's a rough patch. Why
don't you acquaint yourself with our
yard? How about
that? Go to the local public pool. It's
a public pool summer. That's what it is.
The This is a public pool summer. Go get
choked in the water by a gang member
this summer. Why don't you get choked in
the water by a Latin king? Because
there's no lakehouse this summer. It's a
tough summer. This is a popsicle summer.
We're we're in the '9s right now.
Pre-Clinton. We're at the end. It's Gulf
War. It's it's it's there's not a lot.
This is a rediscover movies summer. This
is a Netflix and chill summer. It's a
public pool summer. It's a popsicle
summer. It's a borrowed mom's car
summer. It's smoke a joint on the beach
summer. It is not helicopter tour
summer. It's not epic uh concert summer.
It's not backpacking through Europe
summer. This is a very paired down
simple suburban summer. This is smoke
glass with your friends summer. Smoke
meth with your friends. This is not like
you're gonna be making uh memories to
last a lifetime summer. No, this is I'm
looking at the I'm reading all these
articles about what's going on in the
stock market. Prepare your children for
an old school
summer. Some
drugs, couple of hand jobs under the
boardwalk and move it on. We're back in
school. It's not going to be the
greatest night of your life. I'm telling
you, it's not going to be the greatest
two months of your life. It's not
happening. It's not happening. It's
going to be just hot, sticky, and cheap.
It's going to be a cheap summer.
Everyone's mad at RFK because he's
pledging to find the cause of autism by
September. And that's pretty
cool. Number one, life's about setting
goals. and he's literally going, "I'm
going to find it out by September." By
the end of the This will be the summer
that RFK found out what caused autism.
That'll be this this will be the summer
that we all
remember RFK is going to work really
hard. He's going to hunker down and find
out why people are autistic and tell us
all in September. And I'm kind of
excited. What if it's something we we
have no idea what it could be? We don't
know. Could be canned tuna. We don't
know. Everything's on the table. That's
what you got to like about RFK.
Everything's on the table. I'm thinking
he might go in the direction of
vaccines, but we don't know. We don't
know. Could be household chemicals,
toxins and wood furniture,
uh the the cream for the dunkaroo. No
one knows what exactly is making people
autistic. He has pledged while everyone
else is I don't know what they're doing
in the summer. This guy has pledged to
find the cause of autism. Let's listen
to this guy. I'm telling you right now,
pretty [__] cool. Pretty ambitious.
RFK. The autism rates have gone from now
most recent numbers we think are going
to be about 1 in
31 in 12. So they're going up again.
from one in 10,000 when I was a kid. And
we are going at your direction. We are
going to know by September we've
launched a massive uh uh
testing and research effort that's going
to
involve scientists from around the
world. By September, we will know what
has caused the
autism. We'll be we'll be able to
eliminate those exposure. This is like
going to the moon. You're going to have
a pretty
This is like going to the moon.
You're going to have a pretty good idea,
huh? We will not by September. There
there will be no bigger news conference
than that. So that's that's it. If you
can come up with that answer where you
stop taking something, you stop eating
something, or maybe it's a shot, but
something's causing it.
Well, it's pretty cool that RFK has come
out and said,
"Hey, we're going to look into this for
the months of uh May, June, July,
August, and then in September, we're
coming out and we're going to tell you
why you're
autistic." And it's like a fun summer
scavenger hunt. We're going to look at
vaccines, Kennedy said, but we're going
to look at everything. Everything is on
the table. See, I didn't even know he
said that, but I knew it. Our food
system, our water, our air, different
ways of parenting, all the kind of
changes that may have triggered this
epidemic. He might come back and go,
you're not beating your kids. He might
say, "We have figured out what it is,
and it's the fact that you are not smack
open face smacking your chair." He might
say, "The lack of beatings has result.
You have to beat the autism out of the
kid." He might say it. We don't know.
And he might be right. He might say you
have to beat the autism out of your
child. I mean, belts, chase him around
the house. Bloody. You know what's that
thing Joe Jackson used to say to
Michael? Go get me a switch. Go get a
branch from the tree and beat your child
with it. RFK might come out and say it's
because kids aren't getting beaten by
their parents anymore. So, we don't
know. We don't know. He might say,
"After the research, we've concluded
that children who are not beaten with a
belt multiple times a week are much more
likely to be autistic. You might have to
beat them. You might have to beat it out
of the
kids." Sorry, the answers are not always
what you'd want. They're not what you'd
want.
It's Brussels sprouts, not smoothies
that make you thin. Sure, we'd love it
if it was smoothies. Oh, milkshakes all
day and then I get better. I get better
with a milkshake. Woo! But it's not.
It's actually uh lean meats and
vegetables, okay? And some and some
healthy fats. So, this might not just
be, "Oh, hey, don't give him a cupcake."
It might be you need to beat the living
[__] out of your child again. Fear like
when the door of your car closes, your
child is quivering and you it might not
even be beating them for a reason. It
might be randomly attacking them in the
house. I'm not saying it will be. I'm
just saying we don't know which way it's
going to go. We don't know what he's
going to re what his recommendations
are. His recommendations could be that
you, you know, m maybe he'll make kids
sleep with tape on their mouths.
Remember that's a new thing that people
are doing. They're um sleeping with tape
on their mouth or something with the
nose or something. I don't know. He
might require that. Here's a little
secret that was leaked from a group
chat, but the insurance industry
definitely doesn't want you to know.
Insurance companies profit by holding on
to your money for as long as possible.
After an accident, they'll do whatever
they can to delay or deny your claim so
they can keep those profits growing.
Morgan and Morgan fights hard against
these bullies to make sure you get every
dollar you deserve. When in court, the
insurance companies want jurors to think
that the at fault driver is the one
paying the verdict amount. Meanwhile,
it's really the insurance companies who
are covering the cost. When Morgan and
Morgan, America's largest personal
injury law firm, takes on a case,
they're almost always going after the
big insurance companies and not the
individuals. A recent client in
Pennsylvania just received 29 million.
Insurers's best offer was 500,000.
Another recent client in Florida
received 20 million. Last offer was
zero. There's a reason why Morgan and
Morgan is America's number one personal
injury law firm, the largest. Hiring the
wrong firm could be disastrous. Hiring
the right firm could substantially
increase your settlement. With Morgan
and Morgan, it's easy to get started and
their fee is free unless they win. Just
visit forthepeople.com/tim or dial
poundlaw pound529. That's
forthepeople.com/tim or dial
poundlaw529. This is a paid
advertisement, you know. We don't know.
But what we do know is we don't want to
go to war with Iran. Now, there's a lot
of people in the Trump
administration who they all they always
sneak in these neoonservatives, by the
way, or neoliberals, it doesn't matter.
What what we mean by that is people that
love going to war all the time. There's
never a war they don't like. They like
Ukraine. They like Israel, Gaza. They
liked Syria. They liked Iraq. They liked
Afghanistan. They liked Libya. And
they'll like Yemen. There's nothing they
don't like. There's not one war a lot of
these people don't like. I just want
one. I just want one of them to go,
"Well, that one I don't think is good."
Every war on the table with these people
is great. Everybody we're supporting is
of unimpeachable integrity and the
greatest people ever. Everybody that
we're opposing is an irrational monster
who cannot be negotiated with. We are
just trying to help a people live in a
more democratic way against a Hitlerian
figure who's impervious to reason. This
is every conflict that I have ever
witnessed my entire life since I became
conscious. All of these people Iran,
they've been talking about Iran since
2001.
Iran and in Long Island, you know,
during the Iraq war when everyone,
including me, thought that was a great
idea. Of course, my defense is that I
was 17 and on cocaine. Um, you know, you
would bump into people in Dunkin' Donuts
and they would go, "Yeah, the real
problems I ran. They're going to go into
Iran after Iraq. That's where they're
going to go to
Iran.
Because these people, these gremlins,
these creatures that that walk the earth
have been filled with the idea that uh
that Iran is going to take their Levit
house in Levittown, Long Island, and
that in order to stop that, we need a
major war. This is what we've sold all
these people. By the way, we've sold
them this idea that like all of the
threats that you're going to encounter
in your life are from outside of the
country. And it's caves. There are these
people in caves plotting to destroy, but
they're also really super sophisticated
and brilliant and in caves, but really
smart and they're religious
fundamentalists, but also futuristic
tech geniuses. And they're able to do
all kinds of things like attack our
country. And on the day when NORAD had
scrambled all the planes, they picked
the exact right M. It's wild what these
people are able to do from a cave. It's
really amazing. It is unreal what
they're able to pull off from a cave. I
mean, because they're all in caves and
they're all plotting to take the things
from
you. They're going to come in here
somehow. Now, you would think, wouldn't
it be easy to stop them from coming in
here if we just didn't let a lot of
people come in? If we tightened up
security as to who could come in and who
could go, well, that's silly. We can't
do
that. It's a global world, so we So then
you go, okay, so then what do we have to
do to make sure that no one attacks us?
Well, we have to go around the world
overturning their governments and
convincing them all to love us.
Huh, that seems so hard. It seems so
much easier to just like make it harder
to get into our
country. Well, you'd think that, but
actually the best course of action is to
just go get these people to really love
us and appreciate us. And how do we do
that? Attack them. We attack them. What?
We bomb their homes and families. And
then the ones that are left alive
realize how benevolent and good we are
because we uh let uh corporations go in
there and uh do things. Oh, okay. Has
this ever worked? No. Right. Okay. But
we got to keep doing it. Yes. Why? For
our safety. Yeah. Seems odd. So that's
the course of action that these people
believe.
They believe it because the financial
incentives to believe it are too strong.
There's absolutely
uh direct correlation between the our
defense budget which Trump is now
proposing a trillion dollars or
something absurd because they're all
getting ready for China. They're getting
ready for the main event. Remember
wrestling and the main
event. They're getting ready for China.
But we got to run around the Middle East
as well and we have to make sure that
Iran doesn't come and get us. So all of
these people are Yes. recordbreaking $1
trillion defense
budget. He campaigned as being the
ultimate peace president, no wars
guy, and he's doing a trillion dollar
defense budget. So, here's what people
will have to start parsing out in their
own mind at a certain point
here. What version of Donald
Trump is the version that you want? And
what's the version that you're getting?
And and how much daylight is there
between those two versions?
Um, I think it would be a very big
mistake to go to war with Iran. A lot of
people do. I think it would drain our
resources at a time when we shouldn't be
doing that. It's one of the reasons I
don't think it's intelligent to
continually make the Ukraine war a
permanent column in the defense
department budget and effectively engage
in a cold war with Russia. While the
looming threat of China, which makes a
is has a Taiwan has a lot more strategic
importance to America than the Ukraine
does.
1,000% and any smart person will tell
you that. So the idea that we'd be we
cannot fight wars in three theaters. We
can't be funding these people and
funding Israel and in in Iran, we can't
do it. So President Trump has given Iran
a two-month deadline to accept a deal
that would lead to Iran shrinking its
nuclear footprint or eliminating its
program altogether. I want them not to
have a nuclear weapon. I want Iran to be
a wonderful, great, happy country, but
they can't have a nuclear weapon, Trump
said on Air Force One. Because Iran
having a nuclear weapon poses a direct
threat to Israel. Not so much America,
but Israel is an ally of America. And of
course, um Trump said military strikes
are possible against Iran if a new
nuclear deal isn't reached, though he
said Israel, which has been advocating
for an attack on Iran, would take the
lead. Well, here we are. Here we are.
Here we are again.
And who's this
for? Whose security is this
for? If it requires military, we're
going to have military. Trump said on
Wednesday, Israel will obviously be very
much involved in that. They'll be the
leader of that. Israel wants to go to
war with
Iran because it is in their interest to
do so. Iran backs proxies like Hezbollah
and other people
that have have attacked Israel and
Israel has gone to war with Hezbollah
and it has gone to war. Hezbollah is
backed by Lebanon, but Iran is funneling
money to all of these different groups,
the Houthis,
uh all of the different terrorist groups
Iran is definitely supporting and Qatar
is supporting to some degree. And it
makes sense why Israel would want to go
to war with
Iran. However, right now, it makes very
little sense that a president who
campaigned on being peaceful and getting
us out of wars and restoring the middle
class would
entertain preemptive strikes on
Iran with Israel. Iran has allies like
China and Russia. And I don't know if
China and Russia would directly get
involved in this. They probably
wouldn't, but they I don't I don't think
they would, but they might. It's always
a risk when you destabilize an entire
region of the world that allies like
China and Iran are going to come in. And
now we're in World War II. Now we're
literally in World War II. The economy's
tanked. And now we're walking into World
War II with Iran at the behest again of
Israel, which I don't think is a smart
decision for our government to make. And
there's a lot of people in Trump's ear
that are telling him it is a smart thing
to do, that this is a good thing, that
it's a necessary thing. I don't think it
is. And I think a lot of
people agree with what I'm
saying and that's that we we simply
cannot
continue
to look at regime change in the world as
the only option.
We have to start dealing with people
that are dangerous and threatening
without directly going to war with
them. America's moment running the world
is
over. China is a power equal to or
greater economically than we are at this
point. Probably equal
to. Some people say their economy is
bigger. It looks it depends on what
metrics you look at. India is coming up.
Russia's has more nuclear weapons than
any other
country. A lot of countries are going,
you can't push them around. A lot of
countries are nuclear. A lot of
countries, they're not Iraq. They're not
Afghanistan. They cannot simply be bent
to our
will. And I think JD Vance gets that.
I think a lot of people in the
administration that that I have spoken
to, I haven't spoken to JD, but I know a
lot of people get it and there's a lot
of people that don't get it. There's a
lot of people that don't understand
it
because there's this
idea
that
retreat or
capitulation to a guy like Vladimir
Putin
or the Ayatollas in
Iran is is a sign of American weakness.
And that is the foreign policy
establishment's view in Washington, the
permanent foreign policy establishment.
They just
want war all the time. They don't really
care what
happens. I mean, Netanyahu just goes,
"Even if the nuclear strikes drag on,
Israel may just strike anyway." I
mean, he goes, "We might just we might
do it anyway. You can talk if you want,
but we might just get it popping. We
might go into it
anyway." Do you want to fight I mean,
think about it. Are you trying to fight
Iran out there? Anyone? Is anyone trying
to fight Iran right now? Is anyone
trying to fight Vladimir Putin over
where the northern border in of the
Ukraine should be? Is anyone doing that?
Does anyone I respect the people that
were like dual citizens of Israel and
America, the ones that went over there
to fight. I respect that. God bless. Go
do your thing. And I respect that. But
there's a lot of people that won't be
fighting these wars that just love them.
They're like really excited.
We're gonna we're gonna strike anyway,
says Benjamin. Does does this guy do we
have any control over these people? Do
we have any influence over there? We
give them billions of dollars. Do do we
have absolutely any influence at all
with that country at this moment?
This is like your try. This is like your
kid walks into your house with a new
tattoo, smoking a cigarette, and you're
like, "Young
lady,
what what the [__] going on? You're
smoking in the house. You have a tattoo
and they're saying you're not going to
school. Hey, ma, [__] you. And I need
500." What?
And then as you're saying it, you're
writing the check. You're like, I cannot
believe you're acting. You want me to
make it out to cash? Why are you doing
this? Why are you doing this? Here's
your money. And then they put the
cigarette out and they and they ash it
on the floor and they they put it out
with their boot and then they walk out
and they go, "Yeah, [__] you." and tell
everyone at school, "Fuck off. I'm going
to Coachella to get [__] railed out
in a teepee or something." I don't know.
But the point
is we really have
to start looking at this like Benjamin
Netanyahu is like this guy was like on
trial for
corruption. Now when my helicopter goes
down by the way let's all not it's let's
let's wonder why but he was on trial for
corruption. Then October 7th happened.
The tragedy of October 7th. The horror
the attack. Don't call it a tragedy. It
was an Yes. Yes. Yes. The attack. I get
it. I didn't do it. So this happens.
It's horrible. They respond.
Okay. They go wild. They go a bit
overboard, I think. Well, those are
actually the Hamas statistics. Sure.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. But it's not
good, right? It's not great there. So,
we have this
situation now on top of all and we've
been very
supportive. Now,
Iran I I don't I I don't know. So, we're
going to just we're going to sleepwalk
through that. If Trump does that, I
think it's the end of his term, even
more so than this economic
volatility. I think if he walks into
that war, it's the end of his term.
Foreign Minister Abbas Arachi warned
that a war on Iran would drag the US and
the region into a costly conflict that a
president elected on an anti-war
platform would be eager to avoid. We
cannot imagine President Trump wanting
to become another US president mired in
a catastrophic war in the Middle East. a
conflict that would quickly extend
across the region and cost exponentially
more than the trillions of taxpayer
dollars that his predecessors burned in
Afghanistan and
Iraq. You know, history, the the longer
you pay attention, this is why
eventually I will retire from this job.
It's not because I don't enjoy it. I
actually love doing it. I love doing
this. I love standup and I I love coming
on here. But here's the reality.
Eventually everything just starts to
repeat itself. It's it's crazy.
We're talking again about going to war
in the Middle East. You understand? We
did this in 2003. It's now 2025. You
understand what we're doing again? It's
the same. It really is just It's
Groundhog Day. It's that movie. It's
just the same day every day. I hope
Trump figures out that this would be a
terrible, terrible idea. Now, let's talk
about that car that you own but don't
use. one you're paying to keep
registered and insured that's taking up
space out front and it's just sitting
there doing no one any good. Let me tell
you what you should do about that car.
You should give cars for kids a call and
have them take it for you. That's right.
Just give them the info and they will
come to you as soon as the next day and
take that car off your hands at no cost
to you. Even better, wouldn't it be
funny if I did this when I Bentley and
then they show up and I go, "What the
[__] are you
doing?" Even better, they will turn that
car into funds to help kids. So visit
carsforkids.org/jam. That's ks4ks.org.
org tim that's ks with a k and then the
number four to donate or call cars for
kids directly at 1877 cars for
kids 1877 cars for kids 1877 cars for
kids 1877 cars for kids donate your car
today plus you get a tax deduction and a
vacation voucher and life will just be
great they've been around for 30 years
and they've done this over a million
times this is really the right thing to
do folks It's really the right thing to
do. Why don't you do the right thing for
once, you scum? Call now or head over to
carsforkids.org/tim right now and get
this
done. That's
carsforkids.org/jim. Remember that's
cars with a K. To escape the grid, young
people are turning to mini
retreats, these little mini retirements.
Young people, young
people
are going through it. Apparently, some
young people are spending their savings
on an extended break earlier in their
careers rather than waiting until
retirement. Nobody believes in a
future. Nobody. And they're not. And
they're right. They're not wrong. Nobody
believes this planet is going anywhere
good. No one I know fantasizes about a
retirement playing golf in South
Carolina with their
wife. If you've got
it, flaunt
it. Smoke them while you got them is the
is the like ethos of people right now.
Nobody really is approaching this
thinking to themselves, hey, you know
what'll be great in 20 years when we're
all happy, healthy, and retired and
sitting on our porch wait. No, everybody
is ready to live now and be killed.
That's what everybody's waiting for.
Marina Khazar wasn't sure what to call
the three-month break she took after
quitting her job. After working in a
series of jobs in finance and
technology, Miss Khazar, 30, was feeling
stressed and overworked in December
2023. With a bit of savings built up,
she quit without another position lined
up to focus on things that had fallen to
the wayside while she focused on work. I
had more time to work out. I was eating
better, sleeping better. It was just
like a full reset. For the first time in
my adult life, I didn't have this
looming cloud of work. Eventually, she
came across a term for her hiatus that
resonated with her. Micro retirement.
For most people in the United States,
being able to save enough money to not
have to work is a farway ideal. That
anxiety, especially for people closer to
retirement, has only risen as stock
markets have grown more volatile in
response to President Trump's global
tariffs. Discontented employees who do
not have the means to leave the
workforce have turned to quiet quitting.
acting your wage or simply using their
vacation days. So quiet quitting means
I'm here but I'm not. I'm barely here.
You don't see me. I'm doing the minimum.
Acting your wage means you're going to
pay me [__] That's the level of work
you're going to get. And now these mini
retirements or micro retirements are
people saying I'm being ground into dust
by this hellish job and I don't believe
in a future so I'm going to spend the
money while I have it now to rejuvenate
myself. It they're they're like it's
taking a
sbatical. I agree with some of this. I
like it.
I like it because people are saying,
"Hey, we're not going to make it here,
and I'm gonna have a little something
for myself while I still can. A mini
retirement can take on many forms.
Taking extra time after being laid off
to consider other paths, asking for
unpaid leave, or building in a long
stretch after voluntarily leaving a job.
A lot of people cannot afford to take
time out of the workforce. But those who
do take these breaks tend to be much
more financially stable. Of course,
these are people who have a little bit
of money. Maybe not a ton, but enough to
take a break. And they they look at
their lives and they realize this isn't
going to end
well. Jean Hackman was one of the
greatest actors of our time. They just
found him in his house and their rats
ate them. His dogs ate them. and his
wife, they had a rat born disease and
they were eaten by their own pets. And
that's the best
case. That's the best case. You're a
you're a you're you're a legendary actor
and you moved to Santa Fe to get away
from it all and you're still eaten by
the pets you
fed. This is what's going
on. People know that things are going to
get worse. They're going to die in a
cyclone on a girls trip in Nashville.
They're just going to be taken up into
the sky like the Wizard of Oz, but it
doesn't work out like that. You just It
throws you back down and you break your
spleen. People know a helicopter's going
to crash in the ocean. They know they're
going to go to Thailand, get some weird
disease that nobody knows what it really
is, and then it's curtains. So, enjoy
it. Smoke them while you got
them. That's the mini retirement thing.
It's an acceptance of the fact that this
doesn't get better. And it really
doesn't. Not to be negative about it,
but the American government is in kind
of a cold civil war where people are
using lawyers and law firms to go at
each other. There are different feuding
power factions within our government
that are blackmailing and entrapping
each other and forming alliances with
foreign governments to try to topple
each other. The country and world has
been given over to wealthy oligarchs who
are teaming up to destroy what's left of
the freedom on earth. You might as well
take a couple of weeks in Key West. What
the hell are you saving it for? This
doesn't turn around. This only gets so
much worse. So much worse. Unbelievably
worse. acid rain. Your flesh is falling
off your face. Your children are going
to barricade you in your home and
they're going to be on drugs you've
never even heard of your kids. Oh my
god, the things your kids are going to
be on. They're going to wake up. You're
going to open your kids' room in the in
the middle of the night. You open their
door and they're sitting in their bed
with big eyes looking at the wall
going everything will become a horror
movie. It's going to be insane. I'm
telling you. Take some time in the
Hudson Valley. Go upstate. It's a couple
hours from the city. You don't need to
save all of your
money for when China decides Taiwan's
had enough of free time or when [__]
Israel just decides to launch 15 nukes.
So, I mean, what are you waiting for?
What are the chances your retirement's
going to be nice? What are the chances
things are going to degenerate so
rapidly it's go your head will spit.
It's not going back. It's not going
back. It's not going back. The Costco
family is the good times. They're the
good time. Yes, it's stupid and silly
and demonic, but it's you can still say,
"God, that's cringe." You still have the
ability to call it cringe. You still
have the ability to recognize that it's
gross and cring. You're going to lose
that. You're going to lose it. You won't
remember what it was. What is cringe?
What do you mean? That word will lose
all meaning. You will not be able to
recognize good from bad. You won't know
what cringe means. You'll just know that
a large group of people has decided to
follow a
person. That's all you'll know. You'll
look at the numbers and go,
"Whoa." And you'll see them and it won't
matter what they're doing. Or maybe
they'll be [__] in a fountain in
Central Park and the video is and you'll
go, "Whoa, that's pretty [__] cool.
He's [__] in a fountain from
friends." It won't matter what they're
doing, but you will lose the ability to
know that it is cringe. You will The
entire internet now is dominated by
people who are parading around their
worst qualities and being
rewarded for
it. It encourages
society to adopt that line of thinking.
Let's go out there with our worst
qualities and sell them to the
people. Let's be the worst we can be,
the most annoying, the most desperate,
the the the
most like uh you
know,
insane versions of ourselves. The ones
that we privately
hid. The ones that we would keep under
lock and key. the ones that we would
only show to our close friends and
family and they would go, "Get away. Go
away. That's stupid. Go away." The ideas
that never should have seen the light of
day have come to define
people. And those are going to be your
gods. You're not going to be able to
tell where and when it went so wrong.
Don't save your money for retirement.
Don't I mean, can you imagine what a
retirement community is going to look
like in 20 years? It's going to be a
prison. Just be a high tech prison.
That's all it's going to be. A high tech
prison in the desert with with the So,
and and the reason it's going to be a
prison is they're going to if you have
enough money, they're going to have to
protect you from what's on the outside,
the other side of the fence. Don't go
too close to the fence.
So yeah, if you got a couple bucks, go
to Europe now. That's what I'm saying.
Go to Europe now. You need to wait till
this degenerates
fully. I mean, you're not even going to
know who to be mad at in the future.
It's AI. You're going to be shaking your
fist at a robot. You're not even going
to know who to be angry at. You're not
even going to be able to identify the
source of your pain. You're not going to
be able to. And it's by
design. You'll just be like overcome and
not know what to do. And it'll just fill
you. You'll live in a constant state of
dread. A constant state of dread and
horror. And you won't exactly know who
to assign blame to. And then you'll just
go on this [__] phone or whatever you
have. Or maybe the phone's in you at
that point. And it'll just be [__]
after ret. It'll just it will be and you
won't be able to know. It'll be an
endless stream of the most disgusting
things you've ever seen in your life.
And you won't be able to stop it. You
won't be able to opt out. It's going to
be everywhere. It's going to be
everywhere. It's It's not going to make
any sense, but you'll lose the verbiage.
You're going to lose the language. That
word cringe might be the most important
word in the English language once it's
gone and buried and dead and it means
nothing. And you're just watching, I
don't know, fat people get stuck in
[__] doors or, you know, these weird
albinos singing in a parking lot or
whatever's coming. And it's not even
coming. It's
here. You're going to lose the ability
to know how did it happen? How did this
happen? How have our lives been taken
over by these people? There'll just be
people making sounds. They're just going
to make sounds. There'll be a guy with a
eye patch who
goes and you won't be able to stop. You
won't be able to stop it. You won't be
able to stop. It's not going to There'll
be a woman in her car. She lives in her
car and she'll be sitting there. She'll
have newspapers all around and she'll
just
go and I'm telling you that's what's
coming. Why in God's name would you not
go take a nice weekend in Georgia if you
could? It has absolutely no value. Do
not save your money. Do not wait for a
retirement. It's not going to make any
sense for you to retire. I
mean, don't you want to take a trip
before RFK decides what's causing
autism?
Don't you want to take a trip before RFK
decides what exactly is the root cause
of autism? I'll tell you that our
personal information isn't personal
anymore. Every website you visit, every
account you create, every purchase you
make, your data is being collected,
tracked, and sold. Most of the time, you
don't even know what's happening. And
once your information is out there,
there's no telling who has it or what
they'll do with it. Hackers, scammers,
and even so-called legit companies are
all cashing in on your private
information. And with identity theft at
an all-time high in cyber crime growing
more sophisticated than ever, it's not a
question of if somebody will try to use
your personal data, it's when. That's
why we rely on Identity Guard.
Monitoring is easy. Real protection
takes more. And that's where Identity
Guard steps in. They'll help you take
back control by actively monitoring your
most sensitive information, your credit,
your financial accounts, your social
security number, and even the dark web
for any signs of suspicious activity.
And when something's off, you'll know
immediately, often before any real
damage is done. But Identity Guard
doesn't just send you alerts. If your
identity is stolen, their team works
directly with banks, credit bureaus, and
other institutions to fix it for you.
While they handle the cleanup, you're
covered with up to $5 million in
identity theft insurance. Wow. Listen to
this offer from Identity Guard. Identity
Guard is offering our listeners 30-day
free trial and 60% off when you go to
identityguard.com/tim. That's 30 free
days and 60% off at
identityguard.com/tim. That is less than
what you're paying for that streaming
service you forgot to cancel. That's id
n ti t y gu a r
d.com/tim to sign up for 30-day free
trial and get 60% off. Certain terms
apply, so be sure to check the site for
details. If you're running a business,
you know that every time you miss a
call, you're leaving money on the table.
When every customer conversation
matters, you need a phone system that
keeps up and helps you stay connected.
That's why you need open phone. If
you're running a business, you got to
figure out how to not lose any potential
customers. In today's fastm moving
world, your team needs to stay connected
to your customers without missed
messages, communication silos, or slow
phone systems. A flexible and efficient
business phone system isn't just nice to
have. It's essential to succeed. Enter
Open Phone. Open Phone is the number one
business phone system that streamlines
and scales your customer communications.
It works through an app on your phone or
computer, so no more carrying two phones
or using a landline. With Open Phone,
your team can share one number and
collaborate on customer calls and texts
like a shared inbox. That way, any
teammate can pick up right where the
last person left off, keeping response
times faster than ever. Plus, with AI
powered call transcripts and summaries,
you'll be able to automate follow-ups,
ensuring you'll never miss a customer
interaction again. Open Phone is
offering my listeners 20% off your first
6 months at
openphone.com/tim. That's op ho
ne.com/tim. And if you have existing
numbers with another service, Open Phone
will port them over at no extra charge.
Open Phone, no missed calls and no
missed customers. This is so big. A lot
of my friends are switching to this with
their companies, plumbing, electrical,
real estate, all of this stuff. You
don't want to miss any of this customer
service stuff. I know a guy with a car
detailing business who just did this.
Everyone loves it. Open phone. No missed
calls, no missed customers. Mahmud
Khalil, sorry. A judge ruled you can go.
You can be
deported. While I disagree with this
decision, I don't personally know you.
Louisiana immigration judge ruled Friday
that activist Mammud Khalil can be
deported um in an undated two-page memo
submitted to the court. Rubio detailed
that on March 7th he got information
about Khalil
for so I mean they I guess you know
whatever they showed this judge some
evidence I don't know what that is of
this guy they revoked his
visa he was whing out after the ruling
Cle told the judge I would like to quote
what you said the last time that there's
nothing more important to this court
than due process rights and fundamental
fairness clearly what we witnessed today
neither of those principles were present
today or in this whole process
This is exactly why the Trump
administration has sent me to this court
a thousand miles away from my family. I
just hope that the urgency that you deem
fit for me afforded to the hundreds of
others who have been here without
hearings for
months. Um he will not immediately
deported. His attorneys have said that
if he were order Here's the thing. I
don't want this guy to be deported. I
also don't want him to be like a folk
hero. I don't I don't want either of
those things happening. I want him to be
here and
ignored. That's what I want. I want him
to be in this country and be ignored
like most people in this country.
They're completely ignored. That's what
I want. I don't want him to get a soap
box. I don't want him to lecture me. I
don't want to hear anything about
colonialism. I don't want to hear any of
that. I just want him to be silent in my
country and shut up, which is his
country now, I guess, if he's on a visa.
I just want him to shut up. I I and and
it's not because I even think that he's
wrong about everything. I I I don't know
what his statements are. I disagree with
a lot of them and I'd agree with some of
them. But the point is that I I I just
don't want to be lectured to by by this
guy. It's the same reason I don't want
to be lectured to by
VC. You just got here. Chill. You just
got here. Chill a little. Chill a little
bit. You just got to the party. Chill.
Just just don't tell everyone immediate.
Now, I know you have feelings. I get
it. If I went to Qar to stay at the Four
Seasons, I wouldn't immediately be like,
"Oh, Hamas is a terrorist group." I'd be
like, "I like the
pool. You have to assimilate a little
bit. Just chill." I would be I would not
even bring it up if I was in the Qar
four seasons. I wouldn't even bring it
up. I wouldn't bring it up. I wouldn't
be like, "Well, Hamas is a little bit of
a death cult." I'd be like, "The eggs
are fluffy and the pool is nice. It's a
great hotel. I'm having a good time."
I'm actually having a great time
here. I wouldn't be like, "Oh, let's
organize a demonstration at the Four
Seasons in Qatar. I would be on a fluffy
bed going, it's so techn I would call
the front desk and go, I just want to
say the technology in the hotel is
amazing. You have these iPads and we
order everything from the I mean I just
want to say it's stunning. Actually
think it's great. I wouldn't be starting
I wouldn't be like what about the rights
of women? I'd be like where's the spa?
Let's chill it out. You're a
guest. I'm a guest. In Saudi Arabia, I
don't start going around going, "Why are
you chopping people's hands off?" I go,
"Where's that indoor lake you have with
the jet skis? That
sack." I think people, you're a
guest. If I'm a guest, I'm a good guest.
I am a great guest in a home, in a
country. I don't go in there and tell
everyone what's what. No one wants that.
No, I've had horrible guests in my home.
They bring their dogs. They're rude.
They insult RFK. He's my friend. But
what I've learned is how to be a good
guest. And here's how you be a good
guest. You don't you don't make your
presence
known in
a like controversial way.
You focus on what's
nice. You focus on what's
good. I don't agree with Hamas. I don't
agree with the Qatari royal
family. I'm sure there's overlap. We
both like luxury. We both seem to enjoy
real estate. There's there's overlap,
per se, but they're not good to gay
people or women, you know, and they have
archaic points of view. But I don't make
that the focal point. If I go, I
appreciate the the scale of the
development. You have to
chill. Like the Vex over here yelling
and screaming Americans are lazy. Hey
buddy, you got here a few generations
ago. Just chill. Just chill. You're not
being a good guest. No one wants that.
I'll be a good guest. I'll be in DOA.
Wow, the World Cup stadium is amazing. I
wouldn't people in Dubai. Oh, you think
I would go to Dubai and be like the
everything's made by slaves. I wouldn't
say that. I would look at them and go,
"Get to
work. I'm a good
guest." I would go, "That's an amazing
building." Not Well, there's no climate
regulation, so you No, no, no, no. It's
good. G. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. This
thing's tall. That's tall as
[__] I assimilate. I'm a good
guest. I don't go to India and go,
"Well, this cast system seems unfair.
these untouchables. I don't do that. I
don't do that. It's not my business. I'm
a good guest. I
assimilate. I would be at the Saudi
behanding, not because I agree with it,
but I just be
there. Thief. Well, this
is Well, actually, this is what happens
in my country. We let them run
everything. The
thieves. Well, they just they they run
through the streets actually. How are
you? Good to meet you as well, Mammud.
Very good. Thank you. And this is
Fatima. Hi. Well, I you know, I mean, it
seems extreme, but the reality is where
I'm from, there's drug addicts on the
street and everybody, it's smash and
grabs in the Woodland Hills Mall. It's a
part of Los Angeles. You know Los? Of
course you do. Well, they've ruined it.
They've actually killed it. Do they just
do one hand? They don't do two. I might
do two. I might do too, but I see what
you're saying. Okay, he's coming and he
still puts the mask on.
Okay, it's actually humane. It's
actually quite humane. And they
disinfected after. I think that's good.
What are the restaurants? What are the
Is it Is that one good? You're the third
person who's told me. Fatima, you are
the third person who's told me. That's
the good one. I'm going to see if I can
get it. Well, it was lovely to meet you
and it was love and you're Osama. It was
lovely to meet the whole family. Thank
you. I'm a good guest. I'm a good
guest. What do you think I'm going to
do? Run on the stage? Why are you
chopping his hand off? He's a
[Music]
thief. It's not my country. I didn't
design
it. Nobody's a good guest anymore. So,
this guy's coming here and yelling and
screaming.
Listen, it's not about whether you're
right or wrong. You're a guest and you
have to act a little bit like a [__]
guest. I'm sorry you
do. I I do not go to places and tell
them they should be more like me. I
don't tell them they should be more like
America. That's not what I'm not on this
mission to tell everyone how to live.
Everyone else is. It's
odd. It's odd everyone's just doing that
all day and no one's bored of that.
I don't I would
completely I would walk
down to the Qar
lobby and say to them this is such a
beautiful and luxurious
property and
I'm you know I mean what am I going to
do be like well I think a lot of this is
unfair you
And you know what'll happen? It's just
inevitable. I'll be talking to this guy.
We'll be laughing, probably smoking.
They're like smoking. Be smoking. And
he'll hand me his card and it'll go like
director of business relations Hamas.
And I'll
go, you have to meet people where they
are.
You have to I I don't think that that
that this is the problem. If you come
here, just be a little quiet and fit in
a little bit. Just fit in a little bit.
I'm not saying you're wrong. I just
talked the first half of the show that
we shouldn't go to a war with Iran and
Israel shouldn't start just lobbing
miss. I'm not saying you're wrong and I
get it. And America's based on peaceful
protest, but do you know what it's even
based on more than that? kind of quietly
buying
things actually people like the heart of
America is peaceful protest I'm like but
it's also quietly shopping to be honest
like that's really the way I feel like
yes like when you think of America do
you think of just people screaming in
the streets not really I think of like a
nice mall like a suburban mall you get a
cup of coffee you buy a couple of things
like that's the thing you can quietly
shop you're also honoring the traditions
of America maybe the only you should the
only tradition of America that you
should Like free speech is a tradition.
Protest is a tradition. It's not the
only tradition. Why honor that as the
only tradition? Honor a few other
traditions. Going out to eat, having a
cocktail, buying things, those are
traditions. It's not the only tradition
to go out and yell and scream in the
street. There's other traditions.
There's lots of other
traditions. You can have a family, go to
a little league game, whatever. if your
kids's in it. Not if it's not creep. But
you know what I mean? Like there's other
traditions. It's not the only tradition
we have. Well, America's built on free
speech. Yes. But also uh buying
things. You can do
that. In the same way that I'd say just
well, you know, I I wouldn't say that
the entire country is about buying
things. The entire country is not about
protesting. It's just not.
Can you imagine if I was in Dubai and
somebody came up to me and they're like,
"Do you know all these buildings were
built by slaves?" I go, "Hey, hey, what
are we doing
here? What are you saying to me? Let's
just enjoy this building. It's actually
beautiful. There's an indoor ski slope
in
it." If they said to me, "These
buildings are made by slaves." I turn
around and go, "They've done a mountain
inside.
It's not easy. Do Can you enjoy it for a
minute? And what are you gonna do about
it? This is where I'm at, folks. You got
to meet people where they are a little
bit. This is why I don't think we should
go into
Iran. What are we doing over there?
Like, I think that we just got to chill
it out. The lessons of the early 2000s
were that you cannot force your way of
life onto people at the barrel of a gun.
It does not work. It is not
smart. People like America, the ones who
still like it, because it seemed like a
place where you could have freedom and
you would use that freedom to be cool
and do things that people liked around
the world. This whole thing that like
everyone's dying to be America, it's
completely untrue. It's a complete
falsehood. People around the world are
not
clamoring to be Americans, but the
reason that they used to like us is
because our lifestyles were
enviable. They're no longer that
enviable. People don't look at an 80hour
work week with no health care in a city
where you could get stabbed by a
homeless junkie on the way back to your
[__] rat hole apartment as an
enviable life. They
don't they don't envy having sex with a
hundred,000 people and then ending up to
be completely alone and uh you know
sitting there uh you know watching a
Chelsea handler. That's not um
necessarily an enviable life to a lot of
people in this country in in other
countries looking at us. We're not envy.
It's not, you know, back in the day,
people would look at us and go, "Wow,
that is that." You get your little
house, you have a little life, you have
a family, or maybe you're in the arts.
Maybe you're gay and talented. Remember
when gay people were talented? Remember
that 20, 30 years ago? And maybe uh you
were gay and talented or you were in the
arts or you did something cool. You you
had a bohemian life and you didn't
really give a [__] You weren't running
around trying to make everyone accept
you. You were good at something and
people were in awe of that. Okay. Okay.
It was interesting. And you played
around with gender from a sexy point of
view. It's not Sam Smith with a devil
hat on and his ass out who looks like my
drunk uncle at a Halloween
party. It's not enviable anymore to
people.
Okay. It when our biggest show is a
white lotus with just soulless rich
people floating around a hotel pool and
brothers jerking each other off, it's
not that enviable to people anymore.
We've given away that. People don't look
at it as the ideal anymore. When you
take a beautiful city like San Francisco
and you make it into a scene from a
zombie apocalypse movie, people tend not
to envy that. That's not good
governance. People don't emulate that.
They don't want that. Okay. Okay. When
we're preaching that individualism means
a nine-year-old girl has a beard, people
don't want that. They're not into that.
They don't really want that. It's not
ideal. They don't look at that as
enviable. We're not selling a good
product right now. We're not selling a
good product. So maybe let's work on the
product a little bit. Okay. We're not
exactly selling this enviable life that
oscillates between Christian
fundamentalist lunacy, flat earth QAnon
stuff, and then also like crazy
patriarchal white supremacist [__]
handmaids tail fantasies. The culture
swings from one thing to the next. It's
not enviable. People go, "This seems
crazy." You all seem crazy. You all just
seem like crazy people. It seems like
they let a mental institution out and
gave you all phones. It's not an
enviable culture. We're not selling.
Nothing is cool anymore. Everything is
so uncool by design. These retards bring
the It's so [__] stupid that people
in there are people right now, the
slaves in Dubai don't want to be a part
of it. They go just put another sack of
cement on my back and I'll die in the
mud with my
dignity. It's so bad. It's
so [__] hollowed out that it's the
product. It's one thing if people wanted
what we were selling, they
don't. They don't. It's not fun. It
seems like a lot of work for a very
little result.
It doesn't make any sense to
anyone. The buyin is too high right now.
We need to chill. We need to chill.
We're like a band that's released too
many albums. It needs to chill and then
come back for a tour. Oh, they're back.
Wow, they look good. We need to have
that moment where we come back and look
good. That's what we need. We're just
shoving ourselves down the world's
throat right now. We need to take a a
beat and then come back for like a
reunion tour and have everyone go, "This
is kind of
sick." People are excited about Oasis
because they went away. We got to go
away for a little bit and then come back
and then people go, "Whoa, they look
great." That's what we're missing. We're
just
too out there right now. We're just
we're people are just like, "Oh, enough
of it. It's enough. It's too much. The
headlines, it's too much." You know,
Trump's done some some good things, some
crazy things, but like the way that the
headlines are just dominated. It's all
politics in this country and no fun. And
it's not enviable to people. They don't
they don't look at this and go, "Oh,
it's just constant
political, you know, where's the art?
Where's the music? Where's the pop
culture? Where's the lifestyle? Where's
the innovation? Where where's
anything that we like and envy here? You
know, we're now going and ripping off
trends from other play. We're ripping
off Scandinavian architecture. We're
ripping off this. We're ripping off
that. Like because we've stopped
innovating. We've stopped progressing in
any interesting way because we're just
at each other's throats about politics
and nonsense. And then we're going to
try to replay 2003 again with Iran. Now
we're going to go back and watch a movie
that nobody wants to watch. No one wants
to watch this movie. We know how this
ends. No one wants to watch this movie.
So hopefully JD and Tulsi and some of
the people over there can wrestle
control
back and let's watch another
movie. Let's do something else. Let's
take a break for a little bit. America
needs a micro
retirement. That's what it needs.
America needs to go out to Joshua T tree
Joshua Tree and take some shrooms and
figure out what it wants to do with the
rest of its life. America just got fired
from a job and it's got savings for a
couple of months and America needs to go
out and take a micro retirement and it
needs to go out to Zion National Park or
something and figure out what the hell
it wants to do because right
now America needs a timeout and then it
needs to reemerge and come back as like
kind of a
sexy middleage age, salt and
pepperhaired, old con artist at the bar.
That's what we are. And there'll be a
bunch of the younger countries like
India and Brazil and people like that.
Not old, not younger in the sense, but
like new to money. These countries will
be new to money. They go, "What do we
do? How do we And then America's like
the salt and pepper hair guy at the end
of the bar who's like, "Let me tell you
a story. Let me tell you a little
something." And then you become like a
sage old counselor to these young
countries and you teach them how to [__]
people over. That's what we need to do.
That's our legacy on the world stage.
The old guy at a bar in the Florida Keys
who talks a good game and they go, "You
don't know about Johnny?" And they go,
"Who's this guy Johnny?" They go,
"Johnny used to run this whole [__]
place. He used to run this whole [__]
town. And you go, "Wow, he seems to know
everything and
everybody." Man, Johnny knows everybody.
Johnny knows everything. And they go,
"Yeah." They go, "He brought the boom."
Oh, yeah. Oh, he brought the boom. Good
night everyone.